moviemistakes.com 2003-12-03

# Privacy policy

Privacy policy

moviemistakes.com keeps no personal information on record that is not knowingly provided.

Names and e-mail addresses given when submitting entries to the site are used solely for the purpose of contacting people if issues arise in relation to their submission, and are not required from any visitor. Once a submission is entered onto the site, the contributor's e-mail address is deleted. However, the name is retained so individuals can be credited at a later date. It should be noted that if a contributor enters their e-mail address in the "name/nickname" box, then this information will **automatically** be visible on the main page for a period of time, as the list of recent contributors is automatically generated from the name/nickname field. It is each contributor's responsibility to ensure they do not enter their e-mail address in the wrong box.

I reserve the right to publish e-mails sent to moviemistakes.com in their entirety, or edited - if the sender asks that we don't reveal his/her identity or contact details, that information will not be published.

All images on the site are © copyright their respective owners. If anyone has any questions or concerns about use of copyrighted material on moviemistakes.com, please e-mail me.

GORILLA NATION MEDIA'S COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

GNM is firmly committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users and fostering consumer confidence in the Internet, Internet advertising and direct marketing. We invite all users to contact us at [legal@gorillanation.com](mailto:legal@gorillanation.com) with any questions or concerns.

• **What GNM Does**   
Gorilla Nation Media operates the following interrelated business lines; more information on each may be found at www.gorillanation.com:  
Ad Network - Gorilla Nation Media represents a network of Web sites for which it sells and serves online advertisements on behalf of advertiser clients.

• **GNM Promotions** \- GNM's Promotions division develops customized online promotions campaigns such as sweepstakes and other incentive-style marketing campaigns.

• **GNM Mail** \- GNM Mail assists Web publishers in sending marketing and promotional email messages to online users that have consented to receive promotional email messages. For more information about GNM Mail, contact [info@gorillanation.com](mailto:info@gorillanation.com). 

• **AD Management Solutions** \- GNM's ad management solutions provide advertisers and publishers with a suite of ad serving solutions.

**How GNM's Products and Services Enhance User Privacy and Protect the Property of Advertisers and Web Publishers**

The Gorilla Nation Media Network serves ads to its partner Web sites. The cookies that are employed on the Network serve a quantitative function and are not designed to collect and store data profiles on users. They are used to:

• Report to GNM's advertiser and Web site clients the estimated total reach of an ad campaign;  
• Report the frequency with which an ad was shown to a user, and other measurement statistics;  
• Ensure that an advertisement displayed to a user corresponds to the correct click-through destination;  
• Deliver a series of advertisements in the proper sequence; and  
• Limit the number of times a browser is delivered the same advertisement.

Unlike other global ad serving companies, Gorilla Nation Media does not use any of the data collected via cookies for purposes other than those described above. Gorilla Nation Media does not merge personally identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information, and does not otherwise parse, sort, gather, or aggregate user data for use elsewhere. Non-PII is collected by Gorilla Nation Media through session cookies that terminate when the browser is closed.

Gorilla Nation Media thus has no reason to offer users the choice to "opt-out" of anything that pertains to Network served ads.

**What User Information Is Collected by Email and Promotions**  
Gorilla Nation Media collects two types personally identifiable information only through its Email and Promotions business lines.

**Personally Identifiable Information ("PII")**   
PII is personal information classified as personal to the online consumer, such as name, address, phone number and email address. PII also includes other personal information such as birth-date, zip code, gender, or lifestyle information.

• GNM Real Media's Email and Promotions divisions collect PII on an opt-in basis only. Gorilla Nation Media will not collect any PII unless that user voluntarily provides it to GNM. If you do not want your personal information collected online, please do not submit it to surveys, promotions, sweepstakes, or subscriptions.  
•PII is collected by Gorilla Nation Media when online users respond to a survey and provide it, when they register for an email newsletter, register for a product or service online, or enter a sweepstakes promoted by GNM, its subsidiaries or its partners. Selected partners of Gorilla Nation Media will share information with Gorilla Nation Media about only their online consumers who have consented to the sharing of their information with third parties.

Furthermore, each individual in the GNM Email database has answered positively to an "opt in" question, or they have voluntarily filled out an Internet survey card to receive email solicitation about products of interest. Gorilla Nation Media and its partners communicate with these users frequently to verify their "opt in" status. Gorilla Nation Media also provides users with an explicit opportunity to opt-out every time an email promotion is sent.

In all instances, prior to providing PII information to GNM's Email or Promotions divisions, each online user is given meaningful notice regarding the collection practice and a choice regarding the dissemination of such information. All users are informed about how Gorilla Nation Media and its partners may use such information, including whether it will be shared with marketing partners or combined with other information available to GNM. Users will always be offered the choice not to provide PII or not to have such PII shared with others. Gorilla Nation Media will not share this PII information with any partner company if the user indicates on the registration form the preference to limit the use of such information.

Gorilla Nation Media does not collect personal medical information or credit information, or information related to children, except in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

**How Gorilla Nation Media Uses Collected Information**  
Personally Identifiable Information (PII). PII is used by Gorilla Nation Media in several ways, as follows:

• GNM Real Media's Promotions and Email divisions use the PII to deliver permission-based direct marketing messages based on a user's expressed interests.  
• If an online user voluntarily submits its email address to GNM, or one of its partners, online, he or she may receive periodic emails from Gorilla Nation Media with information on new services or products being offered by our company or by one of our partners.

**Opting Out From GNM'S List of Permissioned Email Addresses**  
If you are a member of our database and do not wish to receive such mailings, send us an email to [legal@gorillanation.com](mailto:legal@gorillanation.com).

  | 

**With Whom Collected Information Is Shared**  
Gorilla Nation Media shares the collected information only as set forth below. Gorilla Nation Media does not sell or transfer the ownership of its PII or Non-PII. Gorilla Nation Media provides its partners only with access to such information on a limited basis. Before any access is shared with a partner, Gorilla Nation Media ensures that such partner publishes and adheres to strict privacy principles regarding the use of such information. Any such use is disclosed to the online user at the time such user submits information.

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII)** \- in cases where an online consumer has consented to have their information shared with third parties, Gorilla Nation Media will make access to the information available to selected third party partners in accordance with clearly stated guidelines.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII)** \- Access to Non-PII is shared, in aggregated format, with GNM Real Media's Web site and advertiser clients who use the aggregated data to determine the reach, effectiveness, future campaign plans, and success of their advertising campaigns. At no time is this non-PII merged with PII. It is useless to any and all parties except as quantifiable data to our advertisers and clients who wish to measure the effectiveness of their campaigns.  
  
---|---  
  
**Opting Out From GNM Promotions Database**  
An online user may request removal of his or her PII information from GNM's Promotions database by sending an email to [info@gorillanation.com](mailto:info@gorillanation.com).

Any consumer who prefers not to provide this information online, can send regular mail to the following address:  
Privacy @ GNM  
2501 Colorado Avenue, Suite 350  
Santa Monica, California 90404

Once a request to opt-out has been received by GNM, Gorilla Nation Media will deliver a confirming email message to the user that the user's PII has been successfully opted out of GNM's database. If you do not receive this confirmatory email, then please contact us to ensure that your request was received and processed. 

**Security and Access to Collected Information**  
Collection from reliable sources - Gorilla Nation Media collects information only from reliable third party partners that have strict and clearly stated privacy and data collection practices in place.

**Protection of collected data** \- Gorilla Nation Media maintains strict data security systems that ensure specific information will not be made available to any unauthorized person. All collected information is stored on our Web server or database but is not publicly accessible from our Web site. Gorilla Nation Media uses a password protected security system to control access to information stored about its users. Gorilla Nation Media also provides stringent physical security and only provides access to authorized personal.

**Dissemination restrictions** \- Gorilla Nation Media will provide access to collected PII data only to those partners that adhere to fair information practices for lawful, non-discriminatory purposes.

**Disclosure and Changes to GNM's Privacy Policy**  
Gorilla Nation Media makes available all of its information practices at [www.gorillanation.com/privacy](http://www.gorillanation.com/privacy). In addition, Gorilla Nation Media provides users with the option to contact it at [info@gorillanation.com](mailto:info@gorillanation.com) with any further questions of concerns.

All email or media companies that provide Gorilla Nation Media with opt-in email names are required to post their privacy policies clearly.

**Third Party Ad Servers**  
Gorilla Nation Media and some of our advertisers use third-party advertising companies, like www.maxworldwide.com; www.advertising.com; www.fastclick.com to serve their ads on our sites. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie technology to measure ad effectiveness. To do so, these companies may use information about your visits to our sites and other Web sites. Unless you are otherwise notified, these advertising companies do not use names, addresses, email addresses, or telephone numbers, and they do not link any online actions or cookies to an identifiable person. Use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies.

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit their respective web sites.

**Linked Web Sites**  
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Gorilla Nation Media is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Gorilla Nation Media encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked Web sites, as their privacy policy may differ from GNM's.

**For More Information**   
For more information about GNM, please contact us at [info@gorillanation.com](mailto:info@gorillanation.com).
